Privacy Policy
==============

May 24, 2024

Introduce
---------

This document (**"Privacy Policy"**) explains how X-VPN collects, uses, and shares your personal data.

X-VPN is operated by Free Connected Limited (**"we"**, **"us"**, or **"our"**), a company based in Hong Kong and established in 2017. Free Connected Limited is dedicated to creating a free and secure online environment for users worldwide.

We will not collect, process, store or transfer your data unless we have your consent. By submitting your personal data to us, and by accessing and/or using our Services, you confirm that you have read this Privacy Policy and agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy.

X-VPN only collects the necessary data to provide enhanced VPN services. Based on this principle, we are committed:

1. X-VPN does not store your IP address or the server IP address you connect to.
2. X-VPN does not log your browsing history, data content or DNS queries.
3. X-VPN will not sell, use, or disclose any data to third parties, including government entities, for any purposes.

Data We Collect
---------------

### General Information

To enhance user experience, we may collect certain device system information and country-level location data. However, please note that we never track or collect users' IP addresses or any other sensitive information.

We may collect users' email addresses when users choose to create a X-VPN account and registration time to allow them to use a VIP account across multiple devices simultaneously. In addition, X-VPN does not always require a real email address, and users can choose to provide a fake address if desired.

When you connect to X-VPN's services, we may record connection timestamps, choice of protocol, network type, error reports, and app interactions to improve the quality of connections. These data will be kept for LESS THAN 48 HOURS and will be automatically and permanently deleted after the expiration. Furthermore, to avoid any misunderstanding, the above data will never include the user's server IP and web browsing history.

### Payment Information

We keep records of users' subscription status, payment methods, subscribed packages, subscription time, and transaction ID (or reference ID). These details are collected to provide VIP services and troubleshooting support (e.g., refunds or adding packages) to our users. However, please rest assured that we absolutely do not store any credit card or payment information itself.

### Analysis Data

To provide better VPN connection services, we offer a 24/7 Live Chat and email feedback channel. Any voluntarily sent messages via Live Chat or email will be recorded. Additionally, we may collect crash logs and data usage information for analysis purposes, solely to identify and resolve any problems users may encounter.

Third-Party Data
----------------

X-VPN offers free service on mobile and PC worldwide. To cover the cost of providing free data, we display ads on the free version. The ad platforms we utilize include [AdMob](https://policies.google.com/privacy) by Google, [InMobi](https://www.inmobi.com/privacy-policy), [Chartboost](https://support.chartboost.com/en/legal/privacy-policy), and [Liftoff](https://vungle.com/privacy). These platforms have a global presence and a reputable track record. They have also self-certified their compliance with [Google Play's Families Self-Certified Ads SDK Program requirements](https://support.google.com/googleplay/android-developer/answer/12955712?sjid=16099780603178146474-AP).

To analyze the performance of X-VPN and identify any crashes on the mobile platform, we have integrated Firebase by Google.

On the web platform, we support user subscriptions to our VIP service. Therefore, we have integrated several popular global payment methods, including [Stripe](https://stripe.com/privacy), [PayPal](https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full), and [Paymentwall](https://www.paymentwall.com/privacypolicy). In addition, to ensure the privacy and security of our users, we also offer an encrypted cryptocurrency payment option that cannot be traced back to the source of the payment being made - [CoinPayments](https://www.coinpayments.net/help-privacy).

Cookies
-------

### What are Cookies?

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your device by the X-VPN website. They allow the website to remember your actions and settings (such as login information, language preferences, font size, etc.) for a certain period, so you don't have to re-enter them every time you visit the website or navigate between different pages.

### Cookies We Use

You can check what cookies we use at our [Cookie Policy](https://xvpn.io/cookie-declaration).

Data Security
-------------

We work hard to protect you from unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, or destruction of information we hold, including:

We use leading encryption technology to keep your data private in transit.

We offer a range of security features, like Safe Browsing and Security Checkup, to help you protect your account.

We review our information collection, storage, and processing practices, including physical security measures, to prevent unauthorized access to our systems.

We restrict access to personal information to Google employees, contractors, and agents who need that information to process it. Anyone with this access is subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.

Your Rights
-----------

You have the right to request access to, receive, restrict, delete, or rectify the personal data that X-VPN holds about you. If you need to access your personal data, we will provide it to you in a portable, readily-usable format (e.g., XML, CSV, etc.) within 45 days. If necessary, we may extend this period by an additional 45 days after notifying you. Please note that you can make up to two requests every 12 months. To exercise your rights, please send an email to [support@xvpn.io](mailto:support@xvpn.io).

Country-specific provisions
---------------------------

### Users in European Union

This section applies to individuals in the European Union and to individuals in other countries whose data privacy laws are similar to GDPR.

X-VPN will always fully respect your rights regarding the processing of your personal data, and has provided below the details of the person to contact if you have any concerns or questions regarding how we process your data, or if you wish to exercise any rights you have under the GDPR.

As a data subject, you have rights under the GDPR, including but not limited to:

1. The right to be informed; This means anyone processing your personal data must make clear what they are processing, why, and who else the data may be passed to.
2. The right of access; this is your right to see what data is held about you by a Data Controller.
3. The right to rectification; the right to have your data corrected or amended if what is held is incorrect in some way.
4. The right to erasure; under certain circumstances you can ask for your personal data to be deleted. This is also called 'the Right to be Forgotten'. This would apply if the personal data is no longer required for the purposes it was collected for, or your consent for the processing of that data has been withdrawn, or the personal data has been unlawfully processed.
5. The right to restrict processing; this gives the Data Subject the right to ask for a temporary halt to processing of personal data, such as in the case where a dispute or legal case has to be concluded, or the data is being corrected.
6. The right to data portability; a Data Subject has the right to ask for any data supplied directly to the Data Controller by him or her, to be provided in a structured, commonly used, and machine-readable format.
7. The right to object; the Data Subject has the right to object to further processing of their data which is inconsistent with the primary purpose for which it was collected, including profiling, automation, and direct marketing.
8. Rights in relation to automated decision making and profiling; Data Subjects have the right not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing.

In line with the GDPR, we collect and process the data outlined in this Privacy Policy on one of the following bases, depending on the circumstances:

1\. For the purposes of fulfilling our contractual obligations to users, including:

Providing users with the Services and Apps they have requested.

Managing user subscriptions and processing payments.

Providing customer support.

2\. For a legitimate interest associated with the operation of our business, including:

Enhancing the quality, reliability, and effectiveness of our Site, Services, and Apps.

Communicating with customers to provide information and seek feedback related to our Services and Apps.

You can exercise your rights under the GDPR to access, transfer, correct, delete, or object to the processing of your personal information by contacting us at: [support@xvpn.io](mailto:support@xvpn.io) (Please note that we may need one month or longer to respond)

### Users in California

X-VPN does not share information that identifies you personally with non-affiliated third parties for our own marketing use without your permission. In addition, unless permitted by the CCPA, we will never:

1. Deny you goods or services.
2. Charge you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through granting discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties.
3. Provide you a different level or quality of goods or services.
4. Suggest that you may receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.

### Users in Nevada

X-VPN will never sell information that identifies you personally with non-affiliated third parties. X-VPN will never sell or trade Personal Data for commercial purposes.

Children's Data
---------------

We do not provide services to anyone under the age of eighteen(18) or under the age defined by local law as a "child". We do not collect any information about the age of our users. Therefore, we have no way of knowing whether we are collecting information from anyone under the age of majority. If you are considered a child in your region, please do not use the X-VPN service, and do not provide us with any personal data.

Changes
-------

We change this Privacy Policy from time-to-time and all updates will be posted online, consistent with applicable privacy laws and principles. Your continued use of our Site or Services after the effective date of such changes constitutes your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. We will post an effective date at the top of the page for your convenience.

Limitation of Liability
-----------------------

It is your responsibility to exercise caution when using our services. You will be personally liable if your use of our services violates any third-party privacy or any other rights or any applicable laws. Under no circumstances will we be liable for the consequences of your illegal, intentional, or negligent acts or for any circumstances that are not reasonably controllable or foreseeable. (please read the [Terms of service](https://xvpn.io/terms-service) for more information)

Contact Us
----------

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy or how we handle your information, please feel free to contact X-VPN at the following email address: [support@xvpn.io](mailto:support@xvpn.io).
